// 20 questions array
const allQuestions = [
  {
    question: "What is James Bond's Secret Service Agent code name?", 
    option1: "006", 
    option2: "007", 
    option3: "009",
    option4: "777",
    answer: 2
  },

  {
    question: "What brand of car is Bond most often associated with?", 
    option1: "Jaguar", 
    option2: "Bentley", 
    option3: "Aston Martin",
    option4: "Rolls-Royce",
    answer: 3
  },

  {
    question: "What was the first Bond film released in cinema?", 
    option1: "Dr No", 
    option2: "Goldfinger", 
    option3: "Moonraker",
    option4: "Thunderball",
    answer: 1
  },
  
  {
    question: "Who was the first actor to portray James Bond on film?", 
    option1: "George Lazenby", 
    option2: "Sean Connery", 
    option3: "Timoty Dalton",
    option4: "Roger Moore",
    answer: 2
  },

  {
    question: "From whose novels are the James Bond movies originally adapted?", 
    option1: "Ian Fleming", 
    option2: "Henry Porter", 
    option3: "John Altman",
    option4: "John le Carre",
    answer: 1
  },

  {
    question: "How does Bond prefer his martini?", 
    option1: "Dirty", 
    option2: "On the rocks", 
    option3: "Shaken, not stirred",
    option4: "With a twist",
    answer: 3
  },

  {
    question: "Which of Bond's many enemies notably owned a white cat?", 
    option1: "Ernst Stavro Blofeld", 
    option2: "Auric Goldfinger", 
    option3: "Le Chiffre",
    option4: "Jaws",
    answer: 1
  },

  {
    question: "Who sings the latest Bond theme in No Time to Die?", 
    option1: "Lorde", 
    option2: "Adele", 
    option3: "Billie Eilish",
    option4: "Alicia Keys",
    answer: 3
  },

  {
    question: "How many films has Daniel Craig played Bond in to date?", 
    option1: "3", 
    option2: "4", 
    option3: "5",
    option4: "6",
    answer: 3
  },

  {
    question: "Which of the following actresses has NOT appeared as a 'Bond Girl'?", 
    option1: "Halle Berry", 
    option2: "Charlize Theron", 
    option3: "Rosamund Pike",
    option4: "Michelle Yeoh",
    answer: 2
  },

  {
    question: "In which country was Bond actor Pierce Brosnan born?", 
    option1: "Northern Ireland", 
    option2: "Republic of Ireland", 
    option3: "Scotland",
    option4: "United States of America",
    answer: 2
  },

  {
    question: "What was Daniel Craig's first Bond film?", 
    option1: "Skyfall", 
    option2: "Quantum of Solace", 
    option3: "Casino Royale",
    option4: "Spectre",
    answer: 3
  },

  {
    question: "Whom does James Bond work for?", 
    option1: "MI 5", 
    option2: "MI 6", 
    option3: "SAS",
    option4: "Ministry of Defence",
    answer: 2
  },

  {
    question: "What was the only Bond theme song to reach No. 1 on the U.S. Billboard chaarts?", 
    option1: "Carly Simon's \"Nobody Does it Better\"", 
    option2: "Duran Duran's \"A View to a Kill\"", 
    option3: "Paul Mc Cartney's \"Live and Let Die\"",
    option4: "Adele's \"Skyfall\"",
    answer: 2
  },

  {
    question: "Wich Bond film has won the most Academy Awards?", 
    option1: "Skyfall", 
    option2: "Casino Royale", 
    option3: "No Time to Die",
    option4: "Quantuum of Solace",
    answer: 1
  },

  {
    question: "Who is the only Bond actor to drop to one knee during their opening gun-barrel sequence?", 
    option1: "Roger Moore", 
    option2: "Timothy Dalton ", 
    option3: "Sean Connery",
    option4: "George Lazenby",
    answer: 4
  },

  {
    question: "How many actors have played M in the official James Bond film series?", 
    option1: "2", 
    option2: "3", 
    option3: "4",
    option4: "5",
    answer: 3
  },

  {
    question: "Which 00 agent is murdered early on Octopussy (1983)?", 
    option1: "002", 
    option2: "004", 
    option3: "008",
    option4: "009",
    answer: 4
  },

  {
    question: "What type of pistol has Bond is most associated with?", 
    option1: ".357 Magnum", 
    option2: "Walther PPK", 
    option3: "Colt 1911",
    option4: "FN Five-Seven",
    answer: 2
  },

  {
    question: "In which 2002 Bond film would you find Halle Berry as Bond girl Jinx?", 
    option1: "Die Another Day", 
    option2: "The Living Daylights", 
    option3: "Tomorrow Never Dies",
    option4: "The World in Not Enough",
    answer: 1
  }
] 